

Jan Arild Stormyr Bjørnstadvegen 3 3740 Skien Norway

tel: +47 413 72 505

e-mail: <u>Stormyr@sf-nett.no</u>

**Personal information** 

Date of birth: 29.05.1985 Marital status: Cohabitant

## **Key qualifications**

First year MSc. Process technology student at University College of Southeast Norway.

Graduated as BSc. Mechanical design Engineer at Telemark University College in 2015, Avg. results: B

Working currently as student assistant for BSc. Students

Worked part time as Mechanical designer in ABB during BSc. studies and as a part time employee for a year after completed bachelor studies.

## **Experience**

Aug.2016 -	University College of Southeast Norway	Porsgrunn, Norway
	Student assistant for BSc. Students in Machine parts.	
Apr. 2014 – Aug.2016	Scandinavian Technology Center ABB AS  Mechanical Designer/Constructor, part time.  Product design. LA-boards, switchgears and substa	Skien, Norway
Jun. 2012 – Apr.2014	Bryggeriet Pizza <b>Restaurant worker, part time.</b> Cooking, serving and delivery of food.	Skien, Norway
Jan. 2012 – Jun.2012	Dolly Dimple's pizza <b>General Manager.</b> Fully responsibilities for running a restaurant, pers	Skien, Norway sonnel and finances.
Jan. 2005 – Jan.2012	Dolly Dimple's pizza <b>Team manager.</b> Customer and personnel responsibilities.	Skien & Porsgrunn, Norway
May.2005 – Aug.2005	Mix Confecthjørnet AS <b>Extra help, part time.</b> Worked in a kiosk.	Skien, Norway
Jan. 2005 – May.2005	Isaksen AS <b>Extra help, part time.</b> Worked as a clothing salesman in a store.	Porsgrunn, Norway

#### **Education**

Aug. 2012 -	University College of Southeast Norway  MSc. Process technology	Porsgrunn, Norway
Jun. 2012 - Jun.2015	Telemark University College  BSc. Mechanical design engineering	Porsgrunn, Norway
	Bachelor's thesis in collaboration with Bandak Group AS Upgrading Light weight taut wire Mk15B.	
Aug. 2005 - Jun.2007	Klosterskogen secondary school (Academically and vocationally oriented upper secondary)	Skien, Norway y education)
Aug. 2002 - Jun.2003	Notodden secondary school	Notodden, Norway

(Vocationally oriented upper secondary education)

## Certifications

2003 Drivers license class. B

# **Organizational skills**

2009-2012 Dolly Dimple's Skien, Norway

- Elected Personnel representative.

- Personnel responsibilities (10-15 employees)

## **IT-competence**

Experienced user of Solidworks and SmarTeam. Also mastering OpenModelica, Python, Matlab, Maple, Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Project and Visio. I also have the knowledge of the general computer usage and hardware.

## **Personal qualities**

Punctual, independent, hardworking, cheerful, humble and respective.

## Language

Norwegian (mother tongue) – Very good both written and spoken. English – Very good both written and spoken.

#### **Interests**

Planes, cosmology, technology, travelling, music and movies.

## References

Will be given on request.